<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>facility management on Servi-tek : A Tribe of Innovation</title>
    <link>https://servi-tek.net/tags/facility-management/</link>
    <description>Recent content in facility management on Servi-tek : A Tribe of Innovation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 12:19:07 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://servi-tek.net/tags/facility-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Facility and Janitorial Cleaning Services to Get Your Building Summer Ready</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/06/facility-and-janitorial-cleaning-services-to-get-your-building-summer-ready.jpg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 12:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/06/facility-and-janitorial-cleaning-services-to-get-your-building-summer-ready.jpg/</guid>
      <description>Summer is just around the corner, and for many of us, that means longer days, greener grass, and a whole lot of seasonal sunshine. However, for property managers and building owners, this time of year also means its time to protect their facilities from some of the less pleasant parts of the season.
Put simply: summer can wreak havoc on a commercial building. Extreme temperature swings, violent storms, and rampant changes in humidity can all cause potentially significant damage to buildings of every size and in every district.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Ways Your Facility Management Partner Streamlines Your Office Relocation</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/06/facility-management-firms-expedite-office-moves/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 20:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/06/facility-management-firms-expedite-office-moves/</guid>
      <description>Relocating your business to a new commercial space is stressful. Managing a successful corporate relo is a full-time job (in addition to your current full-time job), requiring advanced research, extensive logistic coordination, and ample communication, both with staff as well as with hired movers.
Facilities Maintenance Management Can Expedite The Moving Process If you&amp;rsquo;re planning a corporate move, partnering with a facility management company can help streamline efforts, minimize inconvenience, and set your business up for success at its new address.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>