<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Servi-tek : A Tribe of Innovation</title>
    <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Servi-tek : A Tribe of Innovation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 12:19:07 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://servi-tek.net/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Three More Ways To Make Your Office More Efficient</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/07/three-more-ways-to-make-your-office-more-efficient/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 12:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/07/three-more-ways-to-make-your-office-more-efficient/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s corporate culture, green practices aren&amp;rsquo;t just about protecting the environment and driving sustainability — increasing efficiency in your place of business can actually have a direct impact on your company&amp;rsquo;s bottom line. Implementing just a few changes as part of your facility management plan can make a major difference in your company&amp;rsquo;s profitability. Most importantly, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t take a giant (read: expensive) initiative to start swinging the efficiency pendulum in your favor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Servi-Trak Cofounder Completes Ironman 70.3 Triathlon in Kona</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/07/servi-trak-cofounder-completes-ironman-703-triathlon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 12:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/07/servi-trak-cofounder-completes-ironman-703-triathlon/</guid>
      <description>At Servi-Trak, we believe in a commitment to excellence in everything we do. As leaders in the facilities management and commercial cleaning vertical, we strive to offer more than just the status quo. We continuously challenge ourselves to raise the performance bar and redefine what success looks like.
Most importantly, at Servi-Trak we don&amp;rsquo;t just demand a lot from ourselves professionally. We also promote an internal culture where we are constantly pushing and supporting each other as we seek to better ourselves personally as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four Ways Technology Helps Improve Customer Service With Your Janitorial Business</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/06/technology-drives-customer-service-excellence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 12:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/06/technology-drives-customer-service-excellence/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s highly competitive janitorial cleaning vertical, customer service isn&amp;rsquo;t just important - it&amp;rsquo;s everything. With countless commercial cleaning providers vying for market share, maintaining the integrity and quality of every customer interaction enhance professional partnerships, drives brand loyalty, and helps your enterprise edge out the competition.
Technology Plays a Vital Role in Customer Service Satisfaction Integrating technology across your janitorial business can play a crucial role in your company&amp;rsquo;s customer service experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facility and Janitorial Cleaning Services to Get Your Building Summer Ready</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/06/facility-and-janitorial-cleaning-services-to-get-your-building-summer-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 12:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/06/facility-and-janitorial-cleaning-services-to-get-your-building-summer-ready/</guid>
      <description>Summer is just around the corner, and for many of us, that means longer days, greener grass, and a whole lot of seasonal sunshine. However, for property managers and building owners, this time of year also means its time to protect their facilities from some of the less pleasant parts of the season.
Put simply: summer can wreak havoc on a commercial building. Extreme temperature swings, violent storms, and rampant changes in humidity can all cause potentially significant damage to buildings of every size and in every district.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Ways Your Facility Management Partner Streamlines Your Office Relocation</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/06/facility-management-firms-expedite-office-moves/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 20:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/06/facility-management-firms-expedite-office-moves/</guid>
      <description>Relocating your business to a new commercial space is stressful. Managing a successful corporate relo is a full-time job (in addition to your current full-time job), requiring advanced research, extensive logistic coordination, and ample communication, both with staff as well as with hired movers.
Facilities Maintenance Management Can Expedite The Moving Process If you&amp;rsquo;re planning a corporate move, partnering with a facility management company can help streamline efforts, minimize inconvenience, and set your business up for success at its new address.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Essential Factors To Look For In A Facilities Management Company</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/05/three-essential-factors-to-look-for-in-a-facilities-management-firm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 23:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/05/three-essential-factors-to-look-for-in-a-facilities-management-firm/</guid>
      <description>An agile facilities management firm is a vital partnership for both building owners and property management teams. Whatever the scope or sector of your operations, a full-service facilities management company can leverage a wide range of services, strategies, and solutions to reduce energy consumption, streamline onsite vendor efforts, increase sustainability, and (most importantly) drive cost savings.
Select The Right Facilities Management Team For Your Property That&amp;rsquo;s the good news. The not-so-good news?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Ways Of Making A Clean Building That Keeps Employees Happy and Healthy</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/05/servi-teks-three-ways-of-making-a-clean-building-that-keeps-employees-happy-and-healthy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 23:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/05/servi-teks-three-ways-of-making-a-clean-building-that-keeps-employees-happy-and-healthy/</guid>
      <description>Entrepreneurs and property management firms recognize that, from both a people and productivity standpoint, creating a healthy work environment is just good business. They understand that a clean, sanitized workplace can play a pivotal role in promoting holistic wellness for both their staff and their tenants. For these business owners, working with a professional commercial cleaner does more than just make a great first impression on clients (which it does); it also serves as an important investment in employees, helping to keep them healthy and happy in three essential ways:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Buildings: Top Trends To Watch For In 2019</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/04/smart-buildings-top-trends-to-watch-for-in-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/04/smart-buildings-top-trends-to-watch-for-in-2019/</guid>
      <description>Smart building technology has proven far more than a passing facility trend, particularly in the state of California. On May 9, 2018, the California Energy Commission (CEC) unanimously passed legislation that mandates all homes built after the start of 2020 must have solar panels. The newly adopted, dynamic energy efficiency initiative also significantly reduces the installation cost of the panels, which should directly (and positively) impact future energy consumption and waste across the state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four Ways to Run A Green, Clean Facility</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/04/four-ways-run-green-clean-facility/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 12:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/04/four-ways-run-green-clean-facility/</guid>
      <description>The growth of corporate environmentalism has made its mark in industry as companies of every size and scope recognize the benefits of eco-conscious operations. For many business owners, going green is simply the right thing to do to minimize the organization&amp;rsquo;s overall carbon footprint. However, green practices can also have a direct impact on a company&amp;rsquo;s bottom line. A 2013 study revealed that a whopping 71 percent of all Americans consider the environment before making a purchase, granting ecologically aware companies an opportunity to edge out the competition just by doing what&amp;rsquo;s best for the our collective ecosystems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benefits of Upgrading To A Cloud-Based Platform</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/04/benefits-of-upgrading-to-a-cloud-based-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 23:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/04/benefits-of-upgrading-to-a-cloud-based-platform/</guid>
      <description>Cloud-based innovation is changing the face of commercial cleaning enterprise, with companies of every size and scope within the vertical tapping into the power of the Internet to drive both internal and client-facing engagement. Is your organization considering making the move to the cloud? Understanding some of the many benefits offered with a digital data capture platform designed specifically for the janitorial industry can help you decide if it’s the right choice for your organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Servi-Tek Attends San Diego Commercial Properties Expo</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/04/servi-tek-attends-san-diego-commercial-properties-expo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 23:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/04/servi-tek-attends-san-diego-commercial-properties-expo/</guid>
      <description>On March 12th, 2019, Servi-Tek’s tribe of commercial cleaning professionals participated at the 2019 San Diego Commercial Property Expo. Hosted by four premier local industry organizations (BOMA, IFMA, IREM, SDBEA) at the Del Mar Fairgrounds on Jimmy Durante Boulevard, the San Diego Commercial Properties Expo is a marquee event, offering guests and participants extensive exposure to some of the region’s biggest industry influencers.
San Diego Commercial Properties Expo: An Up-Close Look At The Event Each year, the BOMA expo brings together leading commercial real estate authorities to share ideas, discuss trends, and demo products as well as showcase best practices and services within the field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benefits And Challenges Of Passive Solar Heating</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/03/benefits-and-challenges-of-passive-solar-heating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 23:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/03/benefits-and-challenges-of-passive-solar-heating/</guid>
      <description>Passive solar power is changing the green heating game for companies across multiple industries. Unlike active solar designs that require expensive systems and external energy sources to power pumps, blowers, and equipment, a passive design utilizes already existing energy and leverages features of the building itself to generate heat throughout the structure. Put simply: passive solar heating strategically uses material choices, design elements, and feature placements of basic components found in most living spaces (think windows, floors, and walls) to create a smart, green environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four Ways Commercial Cleaning Routines May Reduce Workplace Injuries</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/03/four-ways-commercial-cleaning-routines-may-reduce-workplace-injuries/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 23:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/03/four-ways-commercial-cleaning-routines-may-reduce-workplace-injuries/</guid>
      <description>Most business owners and property management firms recognize the many aesthetic and sanitation benefits gained by using professional commercial cleaning services. However, many building owners don’t realize that customized janitorial solutions do more than help protect the office from surface germs as well as impress visitors with sparkling workspaces. When used consistently, thorough and effective commercial cleaning routines may actually mitigate the risk of workplace injuries.
Outsource Your Janitorial Cleaning Needs To A Professional, Experienced Provider Some executives initially assume that it’s more cost effective to have employees and tenants manage their own janitorial needs internally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Servi-Tek Hawaii Attends NFPA 70E Electrical Safety Training Event</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/03/servi-tek-hawaii-attends-nfpa-70e-electrical-safety-training-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 23:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/03/servi-tek-hawaii-attends-nfpa-70e-electrical-safety-training-event/</guid>
      <description>Servi-Tek Engineering recently held an NFPA 70E electrical training session for its Hawaii branch at the Waterfront Plaza Hotel in Honolulu on Wednesday, February 27th. Hosted in partnership with SI Testing, the 2-hour Lunch &amp;amp; Learn event was explicitly developed to promote arc flash safety and demonstrate workplace practices that minimize exposure to electrical hazards.
Servi-Tek, an innovator in facilities management solutions and energy conservation strategies, offers continuous, relevant industry training that not only optimizes operational efficiencies but also prioritizes safety for both its employees and building tenants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Servi-Tek’s Cloud-Based Data Capture Platform Prioritizes Cybersecurity</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/03/servi-teks-cloud-based-data-capture-platform-prioritizes-cybersecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 23:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2019/03/servi-teks-cloud-based-data-capture-platform-prioritizes-cybersecurity/</guid>
      <description>As a leading facilities management company, Servi-Tek leverages the power of technology across all of our internal and external operations. Servi-Trak, our proprietary, cloud-based data capture platform, is at the very core of all of our commercial cleaning and engineering solutions. Fast, agile, and cost-effective, Servi-Trak’s intuitive user interface and powerful stored intelligence functionality allow us to better serve our extensive customer base by eliminating data silos, accelerating task management, and driving overall business value with every engagement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Servi-Tek Holds Annual National Managers Meeting</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/12/servi-tek-holds-annual-national-managers-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 23:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/12/servi-tek-holds-annual-national-managers-meeting/</guid>
      <description>At Servi-Tek, we apply the “it’s a journey, not a destination” approach to what success means at our organization. For us, it’s not just about consistently reaching the top of our professional game (although, that’s always on the radar). We also recognize the inherent value found in our perpetually upping our professional game. Our commitment to improvement helps us deliver the innovative facilities management solutions our customers expect, and the positive, growth-driven company culture our employees deserve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emergency Preparedness: The Benefits Of A Cohesive Plan In The Workplace</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/11/emergency-preparedness-the-benefits-of-a-cohesive-plan-in-the-workplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 00:05:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/11/emergency-preparedness-the-benefits-of-a-cohesive-plan-in-the-workplace/</guid>
      <description>An emergency preparedness plan is an important component for companies of every size and scope. At Servi-Tek, we recognize that creating an emergency preparedness plan at your place of business can yield a multitude of essential, potentially life-saving, benefits including:
Promote Employee Safety First and foremost, a well-detailed emergency preparedness plan provides invaluable guidance to keep your employees safe during an unexpected event. A thorough strategy gives your staff a step-by-step outline of what to do, where to go, and who to call to protect everyone in the building as well as prevent injuries or possible fatalities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four Ways Building Maintenance Keeps Your Commercial Tenants Happy</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/11/four-ways-building-maintenance-keeps-your-commercial-tenants-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 12:12:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/11/four-ways-building-maintenance-keeps-your-commercial-tenants-happy/</guid>
      <description>Property managers recognize that tenant retention is everything. According to a white paper released in 2013 entitled, The Economic Cost of Losing a Tenant, failing to retain a commercial facility tenant isn’t just inconvenient, but also expensive. Data gathered in the report indicated that losing and replacing a renter can cost up to three times more than simply renewing a lease, making it essential to keep renters engaged and (more importantly) satisfied throughout the contract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Servi-Tek Attends BOMA OC Year End Gala</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/11/servi-tek-attends-boma-oc-year-end-gala/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 23:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/11/servi-tek-attends-boma-oc-year-end-gala/</guid>
      <description>Friday, November 2, 2018, marked BOMA (Building Owners and Managers Association) OC’s 35th annual Awards of Excellence Gala. Held at the Fashion Island Hotel in Newport Beach from 6:00pm – 11:30pm, this highly anticipated yearly event attracted hundreds of local building owners and industry professionals from throughout the region with a primary focus: to dress up, have fun, and celebrate the very best and brightest contributors in commercial real estate management, operations, and services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Servi-Tek’s Kurt Lester Goes Over The Edge To Support Special Olympics</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/11/servi-teks-kurt-lester-goes-over-the-edge-to-support-special-olympics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 23:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/11/servi-teks-kurt-lester-goes-over-the-edge-to-support-special-olympics/</guid>
      <description>Servi-Tek co-founder, Kurt Lester, recently got a birds-eye view of gorgeous Waikiki and Diamond Head – as he rappelled from the rooftop of the Hyatt Regency Waikiki Beach and Spa. Kurt was one of many local participants and supporters gathered for Waikiki’s Over The Edge event, a fundraiser that directly benefits Hawaii’s Special Olympics organization.
Held on Saturday, October 27, 2018, the Waikiki initiative allowed sponsors who raised a qualifying minimum contribution of $1,000 a chance to go Over The Edge, rappelling 40 stories in total from hotel top to bottom for a good cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four Ways Green Cleaning Solutions Improve Your Work Environment</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/10/four-ways-green-cleaning-solutions-improve-your-work-environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 23:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/10/four-ways-green-cleaning-solutions-improve-your-work-environment/</guid>
      <description>At Servi-Trak, “green” is more than just a buzzword; utilizing eco-friendly industrial cleaning innovations is a core component of our company culture. Our skilled and experienced technicians are not only trained in the very latest techniques, but we also use Proctor and Gamble green LEED certified products exclusively. Proctor and Gamble’s line of sustainable janitorial cleaners have passed some of our industry’s most stringent requirements to ensure superior results and minimized environmental impact on every service we provide for ultimate client peace of mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Servi-Tek’s Pickleball Rookies Sweep Round Robin Social</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/10/servi-teks-pickleball-rookies-sweep-round-robin-social/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 12:12:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/10/servi-teks-pickleball-rookies-sweep-round-robin-social/</guid>
      <description>Servi-Tek officially has a new title to add to our many esteemed awards and accolades: Pickleball champions. Servi-Tek execs, Kurt Lester and Scott Sutherland, recently participated in the City of Mission Viejo’s Men’s and Women’s Doubles Pickleball Round-Robin Social. Held on Saturday, October 20, 2018, this month’s event featured men’s and women’s beginner and intermediate sets at the Mission Viejo’s Sierra Recreation Center. Tickets cost $15 per player and, in true round-robin tradition, every athlete was guaranteed four doubles matches with no set partner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four Ways To Conserve Energy At Your Facility</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/10/four-ways-to-conserve-energy-at-your-facility/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 23:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/10/four-ways-to-conserve-energy-at-your-facility/</guid>
      <description>As a business owner, you&amp;rsquo;ve seen firsthand how energy (or, more specifically, wasted energy) costs quickly add up. Excessive electricity consumption in commercial buildings is a national epidemic. Recent statistics from the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) estimates that a typical facility wastes, on average, 30% of its overall energy use.
Reduce Your Carbon Footprint (And Utility Bills) Many entrepreneurs assume that energy inefficiency is just the cost of doing business, particularly for operations in buildings outfitted before &amp;ldquo;smart&amp;rdquo; innovations and technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Servi-Tek Welcomes New (And Adorable) Team Member</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/10/servi-tek-welcomes-new-and-adorable-team-member/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 12:12:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/10/servi-tek-welcomes-new-and-adorable-team-member/</guid>
      <description>We are beyond excited to announce and welcome a tiny addition to the Servi-Tek family! Our co-worker John Paul Del Mundo and his wife April recently delivered the newest member of the Servi-Tek team: Alexus Johan Del Mundo. Born on October 11, 2018, Alexus is now resting comfortably at home with mom and dad, happy, healthy, and thriving.
The entire Servi-Tek team wants to extend heartfelt congratulations and best wishes to the entire Del Mundo family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Servi-Tek Celebrates Staff With Annual End Of Summer Coworker Parties</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/09/servi-tek-celebrates-staff-with-annual-end-of-summer-coworker-parties/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 23:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/09/servi-tek-celebrates-staff-with-annual-end-of-summer-coworker-parties/</guid>
      <description>We don’t mean to brag (okay, maybe a little), but here at Servi-Tek, we have the very best employees in the industry. We aren’t just a team; we are a tribe that works together to deliver innovative, eco-friendly janitorial solutions for clients of every size and scope and in a multitude of industries.
At Servi-Tek, we believe it’s not enough to just recognize our crews as an integral part of our success – we make it our mission to celebrate them by hosting our annual company-wide “End of Summer” coworker party across all branches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Servi-Tek Regional Manager Volunteers At Casa Youth Shelter</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/09/servi-tek-regional-manager-volunteers-at-casa-youth-shelter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 12:12:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/09/servi-tek-regional-manager-volunteers-at-casa-youth-shelter/</guid>
      <description>At Servi-Tek, volunteering isn’t just what we do as a company – it’s a major part of who we are as a company. We strive to make philanthropic and charitable efforts a foundational part of our corporate culture as a whole. Our team of janitorial and commercial cleaning specialists continuously looks for ways that Servi-Tek can serve and give back to our surrounding community.
Servi-Tek’s regional manager, Scott Sutherland, and his son, Zachary, recently had an opportunity to reflect our company’s commitment to public service by volunteering at Casa Youth Shelter, a local facility that offers temporary refuge to California runaways and youths in crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Servi-Tek Attends IREM LA’s Cure4Kids Gala</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/09/servi-tek-attends-irem-las-cure4kids-gala/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 12:12:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/09/servi-tek-attends-irem-las-cure4kids-gala/</guid>
      <description>Servi-Tek, a recognized innovator in eco-friendly commercial cleaning and property services solutions, recently gathered with other local California businesses for an evening event to support children battling cancer. IREM LA’s first charity gala was held on September 5, 2018, to benefit Cure4Kids, an online charitable organization that helps young people and their families fight cancer and other life-threatening illnesses.
Hosted at Los Angeles’ El Rey Theater, IREM LA’s Cure4Kids gala, “A Good Time For A Great Cause” showcased several activities throughout the event, including live entertainment, delicious foods, and a silent auction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Servi-Tek: Learning And Development Is Part Of Our Corporate Culture</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/09/servi-tek-learning-and-development-is-part-of-our-corporate-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 23:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/09/servi-tek-learning-and-development-is-part-of-our-corporate-culture/</guid>
      <description>At Servi-Tek, we don’t just have employees; we have skilled, experienced, and valued team members who deliver superior commercial cleaning services to clients across a multitude of industries. Our reputation for offering our customers the very best janitorial crews is no accident. We believe in the importance of investing in our personnel, making continuous training a vital component to our overall success.
Consistent Employee Training Promotes Our Culture Of Service Excellence Yes, Servi-Tek offers extensive, relevant industry training to each new hire as part of our corporate onboarding process – but we don’t stop there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Servi-Tek Raises The Bar On Engineering &amp; Facility Management Services</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/09/raises-the-bar-on-engineering-facility-management-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 23:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/09/raises-the-bar-on-engineering-facility-management-services/</guid>
      <description>Servi-Tek’s engineering and facility/property management services offer one-stop interior and exterior commercial building solutions to keep your office spaces running at top capacity. We partner with clients of every size and across a multitude of industries to carefully assess your current facility processes. Servi-Tek’s team of experienced engineers and property management specialists pinpoint operational breakdowns to optimize efficiency and productivity, both internally as well as within your current customer base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Servi-Tek Spends Day Seaside With Surfing Madonna Oceans Project</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/08/servi-tek-spends-day-seaside-with-surfing-madonna-oceans-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 12:12:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/08/servi-tek-spends-day-seaside-with-surfing-madonna-oceans-project/</guid>
      <description>Servi-Tek executives, Kurt Lester and Bryan McMinn, recently partnered with Surfing Madonna Oceans Project (SMOP), volunteering at the organization’s seasonal summer surf camp for children with special needs. Founded by Robert Nichols and Mark Patterson in 2013, the Encinitas-based Surfing Madonna Oceans Project is a 501c3 nonprofit entity dedicated to raising funds and awareness for the protection and preservation of California’s coastline. Each year SMOP donates back over $120,000 to initiatives designed to improve the environment, educate students, and help those with special needs enjoy a day riding the surf at some of the area’s many beaches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Servi-Tek Launches Cloud-Based Data Capture Platform</title>
      <link>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/08/servi-tek-launches-cloud-based-data-capture-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 23:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://servi-tek.net/blog/2018/08/servi-tek-launches-cloud-based-data-capture-platform/</guid>
      <description>Servi-Tek has always leveraged cutting-edge innovation in our customized commercial cleaning services and solutions, helping us earn our reputation as a technology trendsetter within our vertical. Our commitment to automation across all engineering and janitorial processes does more than enhance customer convenience. When utilized throughout the cleaning cycle, our integrated software systems become an essential part of Servi-Tek’s commitment to seamless client service excellence, quickly separating us from our competition.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>