<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Servi-tek</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Servi-tek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 00:05:05 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Emergency Preparedness: The Benefits Of A Cohesive Plan In The Workplace</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/11/emergency-preparedness-the-benefits-of-a-cohesive-plan-in-the-workplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 00:05:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/11/emergency-preparedness-the-benefits-of-a-cohesive-plan-in-the-workplace/</guid>
      <description>An emergency preparedness plan is an important component for companies of every size and scope. At Servi-Tek, we recognize that creating an emergency preparedness plan at your place of business can yield a multitude of essential, potentially life-saving, benefits including:
Promote Employee Safety First and foremost, a well-detailed emergency preparedness plan provides invaluable guidance to keep your employees safe during an unexpected event. A thorough strategy gives your staff a step-by-step outline of what to do, where to go, and who to call to protect everyone in the building as well as prevent injuries or possible fatalities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four Ways To Conserve Energy At Your Facility</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/10/four-ways-to-conserve-energy-at-your-facility/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 23:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/10/four-ways-to-conserve-energy-at-your-facility/</guid>
      <description>As a business owner, you&amp;rsquo;ve seen firsthand how energy (or, more specifically, wasted energy) costs quickly add up. Excessive electricity consumption in commercial buildings is a national epidemic. Recent statistics from the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) estimates that a typical facility wastes, on average, 30% of its overall energy use.
Reduce Your Carbon Footprint (And Utility Bills) Many entrepreneurs assume that energy inefficiency is just the cost of doing business, particularly for operations in buildings outfitted before &amp;ldquo;smart&amp;rdquo; innovations and technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Servi-Tek Raises The Bar On Engineering &amp; Facility Management Services</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/09/raises-the-bar-on-engineering-facility-management-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 23:19:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/09/raises-the-bar-on-engineering-facility-management-services/</guid>
      <description>Servi-Tek’s engineering and facility/property management services offer one-stop interior and exterior commercial building solutions to keep your office spaces running at top capacity. We partner with clients of every size and across a multitude of industries to carefully assess your current facility processes. Servi-Tek’s team of experienced engineers and property management specialists pinpoint operational breakdowns to optimize efficiency and productivity, both internally as well as within your current customer base.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>